* Search for:  

    * [What You need to Know About the Risk Factors for Autism – Who is at risk?](https://101autism.com/understanding-autism/greatest-risk-factors-for-autism/)
    * [Understanding Autism in Adults: Signs, Diagnosis, and Support](https://101autism.com/understanding-autism-in-adults-signs-diagnosis-and-support/)
    * [Frequently Asked Questions About Autism Diagnosis: A Guide for Parents](https://101autism.com/frequently-asked-questions-about-autism-diagnosis-a-guide-for-parents/)
    * [Accuracy of the Ritvo Autism Asperger Diagnostic Scale-Revised (RAADS-R) Test](https://101autism.com/accuracy-of-the-ritvo-autism-asperger-diagnostic-scale-revised-raads-r-test/)
    * [The Ritvo Autism & Asperger Diagnostic Scale (RAADS-14): everything you need to know](https://101autism.com/the-ritvo-autism-asperger-diagnostic-scale-raads-14-everything-you-need-to-know/)
    * [African American and Hispanic children were less likely to be diagnosed with ASD than white children](https://101autism.com/african-american-and-hispanic-children-were-less-likely-to-be-diagnosed-with-asd-than-white-children/)
    * [10 Essential Books for Parents Navigating an Autism Diagnosis](https://101autism.com/10-essential-for-parents-navigating-an-autism-diagnosis/)
    * [Behavioral Problems Among Autistic People and How to Take Care of Them](https://101autism.com/treatment-options-for-asd/behavioral-problems/)
* [101 Autism – Living with Autism – Autism Resources for Daylife](https://101autism.com/)

    * [What You need to Know About the Risk Factors for Autism – Who is at risk?](https://101autism.com/understanding-autism/greatest-risk-factors-for-autism/)
    * [Understanding Autism in Adults: Signs, Diagnosis, and Support](https://101autism.com/understanding-autism-in-adults-signs-diagnosis-and-support/)
    * [Frequently Asked Questions About Autism Diagnosis: A Guide for Parents](https://101autism.com/frequently-asked-questions-about-autism-diagnosis-a-guide-for-parents/)
    * [Accuracy of the Ritvo Autism Asperger Diagnostic Scale-Revised (RAADS-R) Test](https://101autism.com/accuracy-of-the-ritvo-autism-asperger-diagnostic-scale-revised-raads-r-test/)
    * [The Ritvo Autism & Asperger Diagnostic Scale (RAADS-14): everything you need to know](https://101autism.com/the-ritvo-autism-asperger-diagnostic-scale-raads-14-everything-you-need-to-know/)
    * [African American and Hispanic children were less likely to be diagnosed with ASD than white children](https://101autism.com/african-american-and-hispanic-children-were-less-likely-to-be-diagnosed-with-asd-than-white-children/)
    * [10 Essential Books for Parents Navigating an Autism Diagnosis](https://101autism.com/10-essential-for-parents-navigating-an-autism-diagnosis/)
    * [Behavioral Problems Among Autistic People and How to Take Care of Them](https://101autism.com/treatment-options-for-asd/behavioral-problems/)
* [101 Autism – Living with Autism – Autism Resources for Daylife](https://101autism.com/)

Search for:  

Autism Resources for Daylife

    * [What You need to Know About the Risk Factors for Autism – Who is at risk?](https://101autism.com/understanding-autism/greatest-risk-factors-for-autism/)
    * [Understanding Autism in Adults: Signs, Diagnosis, and Support](https://101autism.com/understanding-autism-in-adults-signs-diagnosis-and-support/)
    * [Frequently Asked Questions About Autism Diagnosis: A Guide for Parents](https://101autism.com/frequently-asked-questions-about-autism-diagnosis-a-guide-for-parents/)
    * [Accuracy of the Ritvo Autism Asperger Diagnostic Scale-Revised (RAADS-R) Test](https://101autism.com/accuracy-of-the-ritvo-autism-asperger-diagnostic-scale-revised-raads-r-test/)
    * [The Ritvo Autism & Asperger Diagnostic Scale (RAADS-14): everything you need to know](https://101autism.com/the-ritvo-autism-asperger-diagnostic-scale-raads-14-everything-you-need-to-know/)
    * [African American and Hispanic children were less likely to be diagnosed with ASD than white children](https://101autism.com/african-american-and-hispanic-children-were-less-likely-to-be-diagnosed-with-asd-than-white-children/)
    * [10 Essential Books for Parents Navigating an Autism Diagnosis](https://101autism.com/10-essential-for-parents-navigating-an-autism-diagnosis/)
    * [Behavioral Problems Among Autistic People and How to Take Care of Them](https://101autism.com/treatment-options-for-asd/behavioral-problems/)
* [101 Autism – Living with Autism – Autism Resources for Daylife](https://101autism.com/)

Privacy policy for 101 Autism
=============================

Information We Collect

To fulfill your order, you must provide us with specific information (which you authorized Etsy to provide to us), such as your name, email address, postal address, payment information, and the product details you’re ordering. You may also choose to provide us with additional personal information (for a custom order of shoes, for example) if you contact us directly.  
Why We Need Your Information and How We Use It

We rely on some legal bases to collect, use, and share your information, including:  
• as needed to provide my services, such as when we use your information to fulfill your order, to settle disputes, or to provide customer support;  
• when you have provided your affirmative consent, which you may revoke at any time, such as by signing up for my mailing list;  
• if necessary to comply with a legal obligation or court order or in connection with a legal claim, such as retaining information about your purchases if required by tax law; and  
• as necessary for my legitimate interests, if those legitimate interests are not overridden by your rights or interests, such as 1) providing and improving my services. We use your information to provide the services you requested and in my legitimate interest to improve my services; and 2) Compliance with the Etsy Seller Policy and Terms of Use. We use your information as necessary to comply with my obligations under the Etsy Seller Policy and Terms of Use.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

Information about my customers is important to my business. We share your personal information for minimal reasons and in limited circumstances, as follows:  
• Etsy. We share information with Etsy as necessary to provide you with my services and comply with my obligations under both the Etsy Seller Policy and Etsy Terms of Use.  
• Service providers. We engage certain trusted third parties, such as delivery companies, to perform functions and provide services to my shop. We will share your personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these services.  
• Business transfers. If we sell or merge my business, we may disclose your information as part of that transaction, but only to the extent permitted by law.  
• Compliance with laws. We may collect, use, retain, and share your information if we have a good faith belief that it is reasonably necessary to: (a) respond to legal processes or government requests; (b) enforce my agreements, terms, and policies; (c) prevent, investigate, and address fraud and other illegal activity, security, or technical issues; or (d) protect the rights, property, and safety of my customers, or others.

Data Retention

We retain your personal information only for as long as necessary to provide you with my services and as described in my Privacy Policy. However, we may also be required to retain this information to comply with my legal and regulatory obligations, to resolve disputes, and to enforce my agreements. We generally keep your data for the following period: 7 years.  
Transfers of Personal Information Outside the EU

We may store and process your information through third-party hosting services in the US and other jurisdictions. As a result, we may transfer your personal information to a jurisdiction with data protection and government surveillance laws different from yours. If we are deemed to transfer information about you outside of the EU, we rely on Privacy Shield as the legal basis, as Google Cloud is certified.  
Your Rights

You have several rights to your personal information if you reside in certain territories, including the EU. While some of these rights apply generally, certain rights apply only in certain limited cases. We describe these rights below:  
• Access. You may have the right to access and receive a copy of the personal information we hold about you by contacting us using the contact information below.  
• Change, restrict, delete. You may also have the right to change, restrict my use of, or delete your personal information. Without exceptional circumstances (where we must store data for legal reasons), we will generally delete your personal information upon request.  
• Object. You can object to (i) my processing of some of your information based on my legitimate interests and (ii) receiving marketing messages from us after providing your express consent to receive them. In such cases, we will delete your personal information unless we have compelling and legitimate grounds to continue using it or if it is needed for legal reasons.  
• Complain. If you reside in the EU and wish to raise a concern about my use of your information (and without prejudice to any other rights you may have), you have the right to do so with your local data protection authority.

How to Contact Me

For purposes of EU data protection law, We, 101 autism, are the data controller of your personal information. If you have any questions or concerns, you may contact us at :  
[\[email protected\]](https://101autism.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
Alternatively, you may mail us at:  
101 Autism Moshav Tal Shahr

### Share this:

### Like this:

Like Loading...

Follow:

### Advertisement

* [Understanding the Autism Diagnostic Observation Schedule (ADOS)](https://101autism.com/understanding-the-autism-diagnostic-observation-schedule-ados/)

More

### Advertisment

Search for:  

### Tags

101Autism.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com

**Disclaimer:**

##### **This Blog [101 is for autism](https://101atism.com/)** informational purposes only and is not a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. The information provided on this blog does not constitute medical advice and should not be relied upon as such. If you have any questions or concerns about your health, please consult a doctor or other qualified healthcare provider. The author of this list is not a doctor and does not provide medical advice or treatment. Please note that some of the products recommended on this blog include affiliate links. If you decide to purchase through these links, I may earn a small commission at no extra cost. These commissions help support the running of this blog and allow me to continue providing you with quality content. Rest assured that I only recommend products I believe in and think will benefit my readers. Thank you for your understanding and support.

### Weighted blankets

* [101 Autism - Living with Autism - Autism Resources for Daylife](https://101autism.com/)
* [Understanding Autism: A Comprehensive Guide for Parents and Educators](https://101autism.com/understanding-autism-a-comprehensive-guide-for-parents-and-educators/)
    * [How to Get an Autism Diagnosis for Your Child: A Comprehensive Guide](https://101autism.com/understanding-autism/how-to-get-an-autism-diagnosis-for-your-child-a-comprehensive-guide/)
    * [What You need to Know About the Risk Factors for Autism - Who is at risk?](https://101autism.com/understanding-autism/greatest-risk-factors-for-autism/)
    * [Behavioral Problems Among Autistic People and How to Take Care of Them](https://101autism.com/treatment-options-for-asd/behavioral-problems/)

* [101 Autism - Living with Autism - Autism Resources for Daylife](https://101autism.com/)
* [Understanding Autism: A Comprehensive Guide for Parents and Educators](https://101autism.com/understanding-autism-a-comprehensive-guide-for-parents-and-educators/)
    * [How to Get an Autism Diagnosis for Your Child: A Comprehensive Guide](https://101autism.com/understanding-autism/how-to-get-an-autism-diagnosis-for-your-child-a-comprehensive-guide/)
    * [What You need to Know About the Risk Factors for Autism - Who is at risk?](https://101autism.com/understanding-autism/greatest-risk-factors-for-autism/)
    * [Behavioral Problems Among Autistic People and How to Take Care of Them](https://101autism.com/treatment-options-for-asd/behavioral-problems/)

    * [What You need to Know About the Risk Factors for Autism – Who is at risk?](https://101autism.com/understanding-autism/greatest-risk-factors-for-autism/)
    * [Understanding Autism in Adults: Signs, Diagnosis, and Support](https://101autism.com/understanding-autism-in-adults-signs-diagnosis-and-support/)
    * [Frequently Asked Questions About Autism Diagnosis: A Guide for Parents](https://101autism.com/frequently-asked-questions-about-autism-diagnosis-a-guide-for-parents/)
    * [Accuracy of the Ritvo Autism Asperger Diagnostic Scale-Revised (RAADS-R) Test](https://101autism.com/accuracy-of-the-ritvo-autism-asperger-diagnostic-scale-revised-raads-r-test/)
    * [The Ritvo Autism & Asperger Diagnostic Scale (RAADS-14): everything you need to know](https://101autism.com/the-ritvo-autism-asperger-diagnostic-scale-raads-14-everything-you-need-to-know/)
    * [African American and Hispanic children were less likely to be diagnosed with ASD than white children](https://101autism.com/african-american-and-hispanic-children-were-less-likely-to-be-diagnosed-with-asd-than-white-children/)
    * [10 Essential Books for Parents Navigating an Autism Diagnosis](https://101autism.com/10-essential-for-parents-navigating-an-autism-diagnosis/)
    * [Behavioral Problems Among Autistic People and How to Take Care of Them](https://101autism.com/treatment-options-for-asd/behavioral-problems/)
* [101 Autism – Living with Autism – Autism Resources for Daylife](https://101autism.com/)

Living with Autism © 2024. All Rights Reserved.

%d
